怎么样  看起来如何
So? How does it look?
你想问 我能不能看到它
You mean, in do I see it?
是的
Yes.
你看到了吗
Do you see it?
基本上  是个有脑子的警察
Basically, any lawman worth his salt's
都能看出来你带了家伙
going to spot that, yeah.
看来这玩意容易坏事
Assuming that's a deal breaker?
对  容易坏事
Yes. It's a deal breaker.
如果你希望低调一些
Well, if stealth is what you're aspiring to,
最好带一个小一点的
you best go with something more compact--
点38特别版
.38 Special,
短鼻子
snub nose.
隐形撞针
Got a concealed hammer
拔枪时不会挂住你的腰带
so it doesn't catch on your belt when you draw.
屡试不爽  口碑极佳
Tried and true, no nonsense about it.
-5发子弹  -对
- Five shots? - Yep.
自动手枪有多少发
Automatic has how many?
弹匣里10发  枪膛里一发
Ten in the mag, one in the chamber.
如果你5发之内解决不了
If you can't get it done with five,
那就证明你根本不会瞄准
then you're into spraying prey,
那种情形  多给你6发子弹也没什么用
in which case I wouldn't count on another six closing the deal.
这枪装的是10克重的空尖弹
You load that with 158 grain hollow points
而不是普通的冲孔弹
instead of your standard wad cutters.
杀伤力足够大
It's got plenty of stopping power.
左轮手枪是最应手的家伙
Can't get more dependable than a wheel gun.
这个
Here. Um...
把它装里边试试
Try it on with this.
如果你想把它别在腰上
That snub, you'll conceal real nice
用这个枪套很适合
if you carry it I-W-B.
拔枪会困难一些
Little harder to draw from,
但如果你不想被
but there's really no substitute
警惕的人察觉  真没有别的办法
if you're intent of fooling a vigilant eye.
还有塑料的
Comes in polymer, too.
我更喜欢皮革的感觉
I prefer the feel of leather.
有点传统的感觉
Old school, I guess.
是啊
Yeah, um...
放在这边真的没错吗
You sure it's on the correct side?
如果你不是左撇子  就没错
If you're right-handed, it is.
不知道  你确定吗
I don't know, ma-- Are you sure
因为我感觉放在左边感觉好一些
because maybe it'll feel better on the left side.
一般规律  不能从身体另一侧拔枪
General rule-- You don't want to cross draw,
除非你坐在椅子上
not unless you're going to be sitting,
比如商店职员  赌博的人什么的
you know, store clerks, card gamers and such.
无论怎么样  你都要不停的练习拔枪
Either way you're going to want to practice your draw...
多加练习
a lot...
因为如果你笨手笨脚
because if you're all fingers,
笑到最后的人
well, it might could be him
可能是他  而不是你
keeping a piece instead of you.
明白我的意思吗
Catch my drift?
这是什么
What's this?
这就是你要花比枪支商店
That there is why you're going to pay me five times
高五倍的价钱买它的原因
what you'd pay your neighborhood gun store.
枪号被擦掉了
Serial number has been filed off.
所以说
So...
明摆着的事
to state the obvious,
我不想因为这把枪被抓住
I don't want to be caught with this on me.
是啊  先生  明摆着的事
No, sir, to state the obvious, you don't.
先生  我从事这样的生意
You know, Mister, I've been providing my services
已经30多年了
for the past 30-odd years.
这段时间里
You'd think in that time
我明白  最好不要过问别人的生意
I'd learn better than to ask a man his business,
尤其是那律师介绍的人
especially about one referred by the lawyer,
但我真的很想问问你
but I do feel the urge to ask you,
你买枪真是为了防身吗
we strictly talking defense here?
对  绝对是防身用
Yes, absolutely defense.
怎么了
Why?
如果你只是为了保护自己
Because if it's just personal protection,
不如去通过合法途径买枪
aside from a bucket of money,
这样不仅可以省下好多钱
you'd save yourself a potential felony two-spot
也不会因为携带无序列号的枪支
for carrying a weapon with a defaced serial number
而被判重罪
if you'd just buy it legally.
是啊  但是
Yeah, but...
如果你真要用它的话
if you did have to use it,
用一把查不到来历的枪难道不是更好吗
wouldn't it still be better to use one that couldn't be traced?
老大  这里是西部
This is the west, boss.
新墨西哥州不是个文明的地方
New Mexico's not a retreat jurisdiction.
如果有人过来要伤害你的身体
Man steps to you bent on doing bodily harm,
你有一切权利进行反击
you've got every right to plant your feet
开枪杀死他
and shoot to kill.
有人称之为道德权利
Some call it a moral right,
我就很同意这种说法
and I do include myself within that class.
我要说的是
All this to say
我很高兴带着你的钱走人
I'm happy to take your money,
但如果你不是身犯重罪的人
but if you're not a convicted felon,
我建议你最好
you might best be advised
还是不要触犯法律为妙
to bear your arms within the confines of the law.
这是防身用的
It's for defense.
防身
Defense.
我要了
I'll take it.
第四季 第二集
S04E02: Thirty-Eight Snub
多谢  邦妮
Thanks, Bonnie.
杰西
Jesse.
你好啊  哥们
What's up, brother?
老兄  里面像是地震了
Dude, it sounds like an earthquake out there.
对  买了新的音响设备
Yeah. New sound system.
来瞧瞧
Whoa! Check it out.
好震撼的低音炮  你可以啊
Bodacious subwoofers, yo!
这可是真家伙
Serious cannons.
有六个口径十八英寸的炮
18-inchers, six of them.
铝制炮管
Aluminum columns
所以声音非常适中
so they're really, really like, uh, sonically neutral.
扬声器也很无敌
Tweeters are killers, too.
我喜欢那些线条蹦来蹦去
Dig all them lines jumping around.
太迷幻了
Psychedelic.
我现在只想盯着它们看
Kind of like just want to stare at them.
没错  伙计
Hmm. Yeah, man.
完全让我想把旧音响砸了
Totally makes me want to crank old Savage
搞台炫的
and blaze one.
这机器有参数均衡功能
It's got, like, parametric equalization.
能自动随着气压等外部条件
Automatically adjusts the levels
的变化调节音阶
to changes in, like, air pressure and whatnot.
这完全是数字真空管扩音器
It's a totally digital vacuum tube amp
是迄今为止最好的保真扩音器
which is by far the best anti-distortion-wise.
轻而易举就能达到120分贝
It's 120 decibels without breaking a sweat.
站稳了  伙计们
Hold on to your hats, bitches.
对了  伙计  我昨天聚会看到安德里亚了
Hey, man, I saw Andrea at a meeting yesterday.
她还问起你了
She asked about you.
谢了  不过..
Thanks, man, but, uh...
我们在戒毒
12 steps and all that.
不是吧
Seriously?
只吸一小口吧
Maybe just a little bump.
《求生之路》  赞
Left 4 Dead, yo,
僵尸吃了那么多人
the way them bitches get all cranial
当你把它一枪爆头的时候
when you cap them in the head.
爽死了
It's like booyah!
不不不  兄弟
No, no, no, man.
《生化危机4》绝对胜出
Resident Evil 4 takes it by a long shot.
拜托  兄弟  你是在打广告吗
Aw, please, brother, you're fronting.
不  伙计  说真的
No, man, seriously.
那妞  就是你得去解救的那个
That chick, the one you got to rescue,
惹火极了  兄弟
she's smokin', bro,
然后你就像是世上仅有的男人
and then you're, like, the last undead dude on earth,
你怎么能没兴趣呢
so how can you not be dipping into that?
这才是激励男人打僵尸的动力啊
Talk about inspiring a brother to kick some zombie ass!
僵尸要吃你脑子
They're trying to eat your brain, bro.
你还需要啥动力
A dude don't need no more motivation.
我觉得很中肯
That's a fair point, I guess.
好  好  好
Okay. Okay. Okay.
《使命的召唤之战火世界》    僵尸模式
Call of Duty, World at War-- Zombie mode.
那才刺激
Now, that's the bomb, man.
好好想想
Think on it, bro.
他们不仅仅是僵尸
They're not just zombies.
他们是纳粹僵尸
They're Nazi zombies.
纳粹僵尸
Nazi zombies.
对  也是纳粹党卫队的骑兵
Yeah, man. S.S. Waffen troopers, too,
是整个纳粹家族最坏的纳粹分子
which are, like, the baddest ass Nazis of the whole Nazi family!
僵尸都死了  伙计
Zombies are dead, man.
他们活着的时候是干什么的
What difference does it make
又有什么重要
what their job was when they was living?
老兄  你真是出土文物
Dude, you are so historically retarded.
纳粹僵尸不想吃你
Nazi zombies don't want to eat you
只是因为他们渴望补充蛋白质
just because they're craving the protein.
他们这样是因为
They do it because--
因为他们恨美国人
They do it because they hate Americans, man.
塔利班  他们是僵尸世界的
Talibans-- They're the Talibans
塔利班分子
of the zombie world.
我打过这个游戏
I played the game, bro.
他们并不是健步如飞
They ain't exactly fleet of foot.
我是说  有什么难打的
Ohh! I'm saying where's the challenge?
至少《求生之路》里的僵尸
At least the zombies in Left 4 Dead
跑得飞快
clock a respectable 40.
你得引诱包抄
You got to lead them and shit.
老兄  那是因为他们根本不是僵尸
Dude, that's because they're not even zombies!
他们只是被传染了
They're just infected.
他们染上了这种流行病
They got, like, this rage virus.
能量大增  像是打了鸡血似的
Amps them up like they've been smoking the schwag!
风马牛不相干
Apples and oranges, bro.
完全不能相提并论
Totally unfair to compare the two.
杰西
Yo, Jesse,
你的结论是什么
where do you come out on all this?
完全同意
Agree, totally.
刚才是我的幻觉吗
Did that just happen?
该死
Damn, man.
太安静了
It's quiet.
你们知道这里该来点什么吗
You know what this-- This place needs?
你没事吧
You okay?
没事
Fine.
你睡不着吗
Can't you sleep?
实际上不是  玛丽  我在睡觉
Actually, yes, Marie. This is me sleeping.
怎么回事
What's it look like?
你像是在看一块石头
Looks like you're looking at a rock
半夜12点了
24 in the morning.
这不是块石头  是块矿石
This is not a rock. This is a mineral,
我都说了不下十遍了
for, like, the tenth time.
好  知道了
Okay. Got it.
确切点说  是蓝色金刚砂
Blue corundum, to be precise.
蓝色金刚砂  很好看
Blue corundum. Well, it's very pretty.
镶以岩火烧成的母片岩中的
It's encrusted with igneous biotite
黑云母
in a mica schist.
你想了解更多吗  我可什么都知道
Would you like some more detail? Because I can give it to you.
你就这么一直假装对我的事感兴趣
You keep acting like you give the first shit,
-而我...  -汉克
- and I'll-- - Hank.
这是在伊里安查亚的中科迪勒拉山}发现的
Found in the Central Cordillera of Irian Jaya.
蓝色刚玉
Blue corundum.
我只是想说
I'm just saying...
现在是凌晨两点
it's 2 in the morning.
我只是想问  要是你能
I'm just...asking if maybe--
玛丽  就我所知
You know, when last I counted, Marie,
这房子里有4间卧室
there were four bedrooms in this house.
你懂我的意思  要是我打扰到你的话
You know, I mean, if I'm keeping you awake and all that.
我是沃尔特・怀特
You have reached Walter White.
请听到嘀声后  留下你的姓名和电话
At the tone, please state your name, number,
和你打来的原因
and the reason for your call.
谢谢配合
Thank you.
沃尔特
Walt?
在吗  沃尔特
Hello? Walt?
好吧  沃尔特  你能...
Um, okay, Walt, could you, uh,
你能回我个电话吗  求你了
could you call me back, please?
汉克的医药费账单都堆积成山了
Hank's bills are really starting to pile up here,
还有就是
and, uh, in the meantime,
你很久都没给过我支票了
I haven't received a check from you in quite a while,
就是这事
so there's that.
还有一件事就是
Uh, second order of business
洗车房的事
is, uh, is the car wash.
-日 -我们得为下一步考虑
- God! - Take the next step here.
我们需要买下这间洗车房
We need to look into buying this car wash
用以处理...
while we still have--
斯凯勒  你在做什么
Skyler. What are you doing?
你什么意思
What do you mean?
等等  你是不是一直以来都无视我的来电
Wait. Are you screening all my calls?
没  没有  我只是
No. No. No. I just--
你是怎么想的
What are you thinking,
居然在我电话录音上留下这样一条信息
leaving a message like that on my machine?
我说了什么
What are you-- What did I say?
就在刚才  你留下了一个关于
You just left recorded proof
购买一间洗车房的录音证据
of our intention to buy a car wash.
你觉得这样做明智吗
Now you think that was wise?
关于我们什么的证据
Proof of our what?
你在说些什么东西
What are you talking about?
斯凯勒  我们不该在这段时间里
Skyler, we should not even be mentioning the words
在电话里提及任何有关洗车房的词
"Car wash" on the phone at all, period.
沃尔特  这只是个洗车房  不是妓院
Walt, it is a car wash, not a brothel.
我是说  要是我们都不能说它
I mean, if we can't even say what it is,
那有何必去买它
why are we buying it at all?
天哪  听着  斯凯勒  求你了
God, look, Skyler, please, just--
-早安  妈妈  -早安  亲爱的
- Hey, Mom. - Hey, hon.
桌子上有麦片粥
Look, there's some cereal on the breakfast table.
听我说
I'm telling you,
要是你不想这么做的话
if you're not willing to pull the trigger on this,
那我就自己去找古德曼
I am more than happy to call Goodman myself.
别  别  别  我会处理好的
No, no, no, no, no. I will handle it, okay?
我脑袋都要炸了
I could so use a brain transplant right now.
听着  我要去上班了
Hey, uh, I'm going to work.
起床了  蠢货
Wake up, bitch.
他妈的
Damn!
老兄  你的菊花也太敏感了点吧
You're way too sensitive about your zone, bro.
该醒了  老兄  打扫时间到
Ohh. Come on, man. Clean-up time.
立马起身  至少这我们还能做
Right on. Least we can do.
别管什么打扫了
Hey. The hell with, uh, with cleaning up.
给大伙带点早饭回来
Just go out and get everybody some breakfast.
顺便再去买点酒来
Stock up on liquor while you're at it.
派对永不结束
Keep this party going.
说真的我
I mean it, yo.
我希望我回来的时候
I want this place kicking harder
派对能更加疯狂
than a Sensei when I get back.
没问题
All right.
包在我们身上  兄弟
You got it, bro.
都他妈的给我动起来
Come on, damn it.
醒来继续派对
Wake up and party!
你好
Hello.
你是新派来的
Yo, you the new guy?
没错
Yeah.
都做好了吗
You got something for me?
201.6磅[约180斤]
201.6.
多少重来着
What's the count?
201.6磅
201.6.
麻烦你再称一下
Give it a second weigh if you would, please.
新政策
New policy.
怎么了  沃尔特
What, Walter?
古斯在哪
Where's Gus?
问他干吗
Why?
因为我想和他说几句
Because I would like to speak with him.
因为  话还没有说清楚
Because, the way we left things,
我想解释下其中的误会
I-- I would like the chance to clear the air.
怎么
What?
沃尔特  你再也不能见到他了
Walter, you're never going to see him again.
看看谁被饿醒了
Oh, look who woke up hungry.
你饿吗
Are you hungry?
好样的  喝多点
Yeah, that's good. Drink that up.
再喝一点  我的宝贝
Just a little longer, okay, my sweetie?
好吗
Okay?
就这样
There you go.
好了
Okay, now...
这辆道奇车弄了个彻底清洗
the Dodge gets a detail,
还有
and...
那辆花冠来了个手工上蜡
the Corolla gets a hand wax?
没错  手工上蜡
Right? Hand wax.
没错
Okay.
别急哦  小宝贝
Oh. Hello. Hello.
再过几分钟  我们就回家
Just a few more minutes, and we're on our way home.
好吗  我的宝贝女儿
Okay, my sweet girl?
妈妈有正事要做
Mama's just doing her work here.
妈妈在工作
Mama's doing her work.
瞧瞧
Let's see.
做得好  汉克
Way to go, Hank.
加把劲
Whoa, way to soldier up.
你做到了
You're doing it!
加油
Come on!
还有几码而已
Another few yards.
该死
Damn!
上帝啊
Ahh, Jesus!
瞧瞧你自己  太棒了  宝贝
Look at you! Way to go, honey!
加油
Come on.
加油  汉克
Come on, Hank!
坚持下
Keep it going!
就差十步了
Just ten more steps.
九步
9!
八步
8.
七步
7!
六步
6!
就快到了  汉克
You're almost there, Hank.
天啊
God!
太好了  伙计
Oh, yeah. All right, buddy.
这才是我说的牛逼
That's what I call kicking some ass.
太棒了  宝贝
Oh, it was awesome, babe!
太棒了
Hell, yeah.
太漂亮了
Very nice.
好样的
Yeah!
来
Hey!
你是个好人  查克  谢谢
You're a good man, Chuck. Thanks.
这是我的荣幸  朋友
It's an honor, my friend.
明天这时候
Same time tomorrow?
没错  只要我还活着
Damn straight, if I'm still alive.
这节恢复很成功  表现很积极
Great session. Lots of positive energy.
相当积极
Lots.
看到他这样  真是太高兴了
It's just it's so great to see that.
只是...  没错
It's just-- Yeah.
一天一天慢慢来
One day at a time.
我们只能这样了
All we can do.
我知道  只是
I know. It's just
你跟他很合得来
you've got a real way with him.
真是
It's--
你想做全职吗
You want to go full-time?
我们家有空闲的卧房
We've got a spare bedroom.
明天见
I'll see you tomorrow.
你今天真的很坚强
You were so strong today.
你是不是有胃口了  我肯定你饿了
Did you work up an appetite? I'm sure that you did.
我正在想着今晚要做什么
Listen, I was thinking about cooking tonight.
-所以  -玛丽
- So-  - Marie.
出去吧
Get out.
来得正好
Oh, yo, about time.
我的天
Oh, my God.
披萨怎么回事  都没切
Yo, what's up with the pie, man? It ain't cut.
没错  这可是个小创举
Yeah. Right. That's the gimmick.
-什么创举  -这家披萨店
- What gimmick? - This place.
披萨从不切开
They don't cut their pizza,
为你省下切的钱
and they pass the savings on to you.
省什么钱  切个披萨能花几个钱
What savings? How much can it be to cut a damn pizza?
这就像是  搞民主  兄弟
Maybe it's, like, democratic, bro, you know?
自己砍圣诞树  自己切披萨
Cut your own Christmas tree. Cut your own pizza.
对啊  很民主
Yeah. It's democratic.
这我要怎么吃啊
What am I supposed to do with this?
别对它撒气
Don't sweat it, yo.
你有剪刀吗
You got some, like, scissors?
我来把它全分开
I will cut this bitch up good.
请进
Yo, come in!
去开下门吧
Hey, would you mind?
我假设一年能做一千万张披萨
I figure you make, like, 10 million pizzas a year.
每张披萨  切开花去十秒钟
Each pizza takes, like, 10 seconds to cut.
换算成劳动工时  就是
In man hours, that's--
我算不清
I don't know.
很久吧
A lot?
杰西
Hey, Jesse.
找你的
You got, um, yeah.
你还好吗
So, uh, how you doing?
还在适应
I'm dealing.
布洛克怎么样了
How's Brock?
很好  他就在...
Good. He's...
布洛克  宝贝  在车里等好吗
Brock, honey, wait in the car, okay?
让大人聊一会儿
Let the grownups speak.
去吧  小家伙  我们一会儿聊
Go on, little man. We'll catch up later.
我想你知道我一直在打给你
Guess you know I've been calling.
是啊  我工作真的很忙
Yeah, um, I'm really busy at work and--
杰西  我来这儿不是来听你找借口的
Jesse, I'm not here to make you come up with excuses.
你有自己的事情
You got other things going on.
我明白
I get it.
只是有件事我们必须聊聊
There's just one thing you and me got to talk about.
就是这个
And that's this.
汤玛斯被杀之后  那个街区
After Tomás was murdered, two dudes from the block,
过去常跟他一起鬼混的两个人  被车撞了
a couple bangers he used to hang with, get run over,
其中一个头部中枪
one of them shot in the head.
就在当晚  我在邮箱里发现了这个
Same night, I get this in my mailbox.
这是你放的吗
This was you?
你知道吗
You know what?
无论你和杀我弟弟的凶手有什么关系
Whatever it is you had to do with my brother's killers,
我都不想知道
I don't want to know.
但你必须告诉我一件事
But you got to tell me one thing.
会有人来要这笔钱吗
Is someone gonna come looking for this?
不会
No.
那我拿这些钱来做什么
What exactly am I supposed to do with this?
这些钱能让你和布洛克
Use it to get you and Brock
搬离那个恶臭的贫民窟
out of that shit hole of a neighborhood.
或者拿着这些钱继续吸
Or you can go out and spend it on glass,
这我就管不了你了
and I'd have no way of stopping you.
但我相信你绝对不会这么做
But I got to believe you won't do that.
沃尔特  回家去吧
Go home, Walter.
您好
How you doing?
砖块
Ton of bricks?
石头
Rocks.
我可以帮你把它们推进去
You, uh, want me to wheel them inside for you?
谢谢你
Thank you.
玛丽  是我的矿石到了吗
Marie, is that my minerals?
是的  汉克
Yes, Hank.
有多少盒
How many boxes?
我不确定
I don't know--
三个  四个  上百个
Three, four, a hundred,
百万个
a million.
我不知道
I don't know.
你检查过破损吗
Did you check them for damage?
汉克  这些是石头
They're rocks, Hank.
不是  它们是矿石
No, they're minerals.
玛丽  这里有一些特别精美易碎的
Jesus, Marie, I got some geodes coming
晶洞玉石
that are very delicate, all right?
如果包装有破损  我就要退货
And I will not accept any boxes that have damage.
我跟你讲  那些送货的混蛋
Those delivery jackoffs, I'm telling you--
我可不能就这么受他们欺负
I'm not getting ass raped by those bastards, all right?
亲爱的
Just--
求你  能检查一下吗
Honey, would you check?
求你检查一下
Just check, please?
别那么浪费
Stop wasting it.
听着  告诉你哥哥
Look, tell your brother
如果他明天还不来上班
that if he doesn't show up tomorrow,
以后就别来了
I'm going to have to fire him.
回去干活  别那么多借口
So now go back. And no more excuses.
沃利兹先生  我叫斯凯勒・怀特
Mr. Wolynetz, my name is Skyler White.
您好
How do you do?
你想买我的洗车场
You want to buy my car wash.
是的  而且如果您愿意的话
I do. And I am prepared to talk numbers right now,
我今天是来跟你谈价钱的
if you'd like.
你以为这是份清闲的活儿吗
Do you think this is an easy job?
你愿意哈下腰
You are willing to get down on your hands and knees
蹭这擦那像个女佣一样
and scrub like a house maid
更何况那些化学品会灼伤你的肌肤
with all the chemicals eating into your nice skin
会刺痛你的双眼
and stinging in your eyes?
我对洗车行业有些许了解
Well, I know a thing or two about scrubbing.
还有其他建议吗
Any other advice for me?
因为我是很认真地在考虑这件事情
Because I am serious about this.
很好
Good.
我也很认真
I am serious, too.
我在这行辛辛苦苦白手起家
I have worked 30 years of building this business from nothing,
30年才建造了这家洗车场
with my own hands and my own sweat and blood.
我真心敬佩您
I can appreciate that, truly.
考虑到这点
So, with that in mind,
您能给我一个具体的数字吗
is there a figure you can quote me?
一个能让您满意的数字
One which you think would adequately--
一千万
$10 million.
不如谈一下879,000这个数字吧
Well, let's try 879,000.
你怎么得出这个数字呢
Where do you come up with this number?
瞎编出来的数字
You pull it from your behind?
洗车场平日里
On a typical day,
每小时能洗19辆车
you manage 19 cars per hour.
经推断  加上手工打蜡及装饰品等
Extrapolating, I added the extra revenues
预算外收入
for hand waxes and detailing,
再减去日常开支  薪金  维修费
subtracted your overhead and salary and maintenance,
运转费  折旧
operating fees, depreciation,
我从阿尔伯开克地区相同等级品牌
which I obtained from comparable businesses
得到的数据
in the Albuquerque area,
使我大概得出你这里每年的资金流动
giving me an estimate of your annual cash flow here,
我运用了产业标准乘数
to which I applied the industry standard multiplier
并加上你不动产的市价
and added the market value of your real estate,
得出总值大约为829000这个数字
giving me a total estimated value of $829,000,
于此同时我又很大方的多加了五万
on top of which I generously added an extra $50,000...
作为敬意
so as not to be insulting.
两千万
$20 million.
沃利兹先生
Okay, Mr. Wolynetz, this--
这是给沃尔特・怀特的价钱
This is the price for Walter White.
你以为我不知道你是谁
You don't think I know who you are?
我记得可清楚了
I remember.
我从未想过要冒名顶替
Well, I have not pretended to be any--
你的丈夫  他擅离职守
Your husband, he quit without giving me notice.
他弄坏了我的空气清新器
He broke my air fresheners.
他诅咒我  还抓自己来挑衅我
He cursed at me and grabbed himself.
现在他想买我的洗车场
And now he wants to buy my car wash.
又完全不像个男人来直面我说出这个要求
But he's not man enough to come in here and face me himself.
-而是派自己的女人来  -什么
- Instead, he sends his woman. - Excuse me?
沃尔特・怀特想买我的洗车场
Walter White wants to buy my car wash.
我给他开的价钱就是两千万
The price he pays is $20 million.
你可以走了
Now please leave.
你近期是否因空难失去最心爱的人
Have you recently lost a loved one on an aviation disaster?
你近期是否因飞机残骸
Have you suffered injury,
甚至跌落下来的身体残骸
shock to the senses,
受过感官方面的惊吓
or property damage as a result of airplane debris
或财产损失
or, God forbid, falling body parts?
告诉我  由我索尔・古德曼帮您解决
Then call me, Saul Goodman.
无需多言
It goes without saying
我能为您赢得
that the six-, seven-,
六位  七位  甚至是八位数字的
perhaps even eight-figure cash settlement
现金补偿
that I can win for you
都将永远无法填补悲剧发生
will never fill the hole in your heart
而造成您内心的空虚
caused by your tragic loss,
但您需要公正
but you deserve justice.
若您想扭转局势
So if you want to tip the scales
赢得官司
back in your favor,
就找索尔
better call Saul.
索尔・古德曼律师
Saul Goodman, attorney at law.
505-503-4455
505-503-4455.
提供西班牙语服务
Se habla espanol.
如果你打算一直跟踪下去
You might want to learn how to tail better
最好能学几招
if you're planning on making a habit of it.
能请你喝一杯吗
May I buy you a drink?
等你喝完  再来一杯
Next round, when you're done.
请吧  你赚得可比我多的去了
Why not? You make a hell of a lot more than I do.
给他再来一杯
Uh, another round for him,
我也一样  不加冰
and I'll have the same. No ice.
我觉得我需要解释下
I feel like I need to explain myself.
希望你能够理解
There were some actions that I took
我的某些举动
which I want you to understand.
我并不希望发生这一切
I didn't want any of this to happen.
我的所作所为
Everything I did
都是出于对伙伴的忠诚
I did out of loyalty to my partner,
当然了  后来
and then, later, of course,
纯粹是出于正当防卫
it was purely out of self-defense.
希望你能理解
I hope you can appreciate that...
正如我能理解
just like I appreciated that, uh--
我能理解  你意图杀我
I appreciate that when you were going to kill me
只是在奉命行事
you were simply following orders.
我完全理解
I get that completely.
且不会心怀怨恨
And I harbor no ill will.
那我就放心了
Well, there's a load off my mind.
麦克  我是想说
Mike, I'm trying to tell you--
我懂
I get it.
行了
Fine.
喝酒吧  沃尔特
Drink up, Walter.
最近几周噩耗连连
Hell of a last couple of weeks.
不禁叫人怀疑自己的处境
Makes a man wonder exactly where he stands.
我是说
I mean, I--
维克多死后
I cannot be alone in feeling this way.
不可能只有我有这感觉吧
Not after what happened to Victor.
那么
So...
带手枪干嘛
what's with the piece?
你右边腰带上
Right hip inside your waistband.
那天在实验室我就注意到了
I noticed it the other day at the lab.
带着它能让你安心吧
You wear it if it makes you feel better,
但若真到事态严重  它可帮不上忙
but if push comes to shove, it's not going to help.
麦克  非得要我直说吗
Mike, do I have to come right out and say this?
我们俩  是一条船上的蚂蚱
You and I, we're in the same boat.
还是喝你的酒吧
Drink your drink.
维克多死了  下一个可能就是你
If it happened to Victor, it could happen to you.
那算什么
And-- and what the hell was that anyway?
讯息吗
Hmm? A message?
他割断他的喉咙只为传递一条讯息吗
He cuts a man's throat just to send a message?
你是赢家  沃尔特
You won, Walter.
你得到了工作
You got the job.
帮你自己个忙
Do yourself a favor
知足常乐吧
and learn to take yes for an answer.
我现在是有工作了  但能做多久呢
Yeah, I got the job, but for how long?
让我和他共处一室
Get me in a room with him.
麦克  只要你让我们共处一室
Mike, just get me in a room,
剩下的交给我
and I'll do the rest.
你说完了吗
You done?
说完了
Yeah.
谢谢你的酒
Thanks for the drink.
哥们  你的派对超赞  兄弟
Hey, my man, you know how to party, brother.
爽啊  爽
Epic! Epic!
怎么  你们两个要上哪里去
Uh, seriously, where are you two going?
杰西  我连着三天  几乎都没怎么合眼
Jesse, I've been awake for, like, three straight days.
我都快变凹凸曼了
I'm turning into a Sleestak.
那就在这里过夜吧  又不是没地方
So crash here. It's not like I ain't got the space.
这主意不错
Yeah, that's cool and all,
但我好像养了只猫
but I think I got, like, this cat.
我该  回去喂食了
I think I'm, like, supposed to feed it.
随便吧  个贱人
Whatever, you little bitch.
那你呢  你留下吗
What about you? You sticking,
还是要我插下你的菊花或是给你找个骚货
or do I got to flip you over and check you for a slizz?
兄弟  我都快死了
Bro, I'm kind of pushing flowers here, yo.
这没什么好骄傲的  但我说的可是大实话
I ain't proud of it, but it's God's honest truth.
兄弟  你知道我们和你有兄弟情谊
Hell, brother, you know we got man love for you.
既然你又干回这行了
Now that you're back in the mix,
简直前途无量啊
it's like nothing but good days ahead.
好日子正等着你呢
Plenty of time to pace it out is all I'm saying.
对
Yeah.
没错  朋友
Yeah, man.
一点没错
Totally.
不如  下星期继续
I was thinking, like, next week?
行啊  下星期继续
Yeah, sure, man. Next week.
我们没事吧
Are we cool?
没事
We are cool.